const data = [
  {
    answer: 'JavaScript',
    question:
      'What is the most widely used programming language for web development?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'HTML',
    question: 'Which markup language is used to structure content on the web?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'CSS',
    question: 'What is the styling language used for designing web pages?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Browser',
    question:
      'What software application is commonly used to access and navigate the internet?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'SEO',
    question:
      'What acronym refers to the practice of optimizing websites to rank higher in search engine results?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'GitHub',
    question:
      'Which platform is widely used for version control and collaborative coding projects?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'AJAX',
    question:
      'What technology allows asynchronous communication between a web browser and a server?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'JSON',
    question:
      'What format is commonly used for data interchange between a server and a web application?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'DNS',
    question:
      'What system translates domain names to IP addresses on the internet?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Security',
    question:
      'What aspect of web development focuses on protecting websites and web applications from cyber threats?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Grid',
    question:
      'What CSS layout system allows the design of complex web layouts with rows and columns?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Sass',
    question:
      'Which CSS preprocessor extends the functionality of CSS by providing features like variables and nested rules?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'HTTPS',
    question:
      'What protocol is used for secure data communication over a computer network, commonly used in web browsing?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Closure',
    question:
      'What term in JS refers to the ability of a function to access variables from its outer scope even after the function has finished execution?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Callback',
    question:
      'What is a function passed as an argument to another function, which will be invoked later in the program execution process?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Promise',
    question:
      'What is an object in JS representing the eventual completion or failure of an asynchronous operation?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Hoisting',
    question:
      'What is a behavior in JS where variable and function declarations are moved to the top of their containing scope during the compilation phase?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Event',
    question:
      'What term in JS refers to an action or occurrence detected by the program that can be responded to, such as a user clicking a button?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Arrow',
    question:
      'What concise syntax introduced in ES 6 allows the creation of anonymous functions more easily, often used for short, one-line functions?',
  },
  {
    answer: 'Truthy',
    question:
      'What term in JS describes a value that is considered true when evaluated in a Boolean context, even if it is not a strict Boolean true value?',
  }
];

export { data };
